[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Thorium?", "correct_answer": "Th", "incorrect_answers": ["T", "Fe", "Tr"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is said that twins develop their own language, called this.", "correct_answer": "Idioglossia", "incorrect_answers": ["Sindarin", "Quenya", "Klingon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cities is known as the Milk Capital of the World?", "correct_answer": "Harvard, Illinois", "incorrect_answers": ["Genoa, Italy", "Bern, Switzerland", "Bombay, India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Arabic term, Maghrib represent?", "correct_answer": "Sunset prayers", "incorrect_answers": ["City of the believers", "Place of peace", "Prison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Willy Wonka fire all of his workers, including Charlies grandpa, in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "He was afraid of spies.", "incorrect_answers": ["He accused them of being lazy.", "He hated to see people around him.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Edmund Hillary, the first mountaineer to reach mount Everest, was from what country?", "correct_answer": "New Zealand", "incorrect_answers": ["The USA", "Great Britain", "Norway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to be classified as a Category 5 hurricane, the storm must have what winds speeds?", "correct_answer": "155mph", "incorrect_answers": ["135mph", "125mph", "145mph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Maltese Falcon in the 1941 movie The Maltese Falcon?", "correct_answer": "An art piece", "incorrect_answers": ["An aircraft", "A nickname of a murderer", "A diamond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city in Switzerland is the headquarters of the World Trade Organization (WTO) located?", "correct_answer": "Geneva", "incorrect_answers": ["Berne", "Born", "Bamako"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the garden strawberry first bred in 1740?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "India", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played Treasury Secretary William Cleary in the great movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Christopher Walken", "incorrect_answers": ["Kurt Valdheim, Jr.", "Henry Gibson", "Carson Elrod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the approximate distance between the Moon and the Earth?", "correct_answer": "384,000 kilometers", "incorrect_answers": ["384,000 miles", "93,000,000 miles", "384,000 meters"]}]